我去太空进行了一项为期十三个月的单人任务
I went to space on a 13-month solo mission.
我并非独自归来
I didn't come home alone.
我丈夫发明了一种栩栩如生的机器人  人工生命
My husband created a lifelike android called a Humanich.
他叫伊森  他是原型
His name is Ethan-- he's the prototype.
这是一个关于地球的故事
This is a story about Earth...
伊森
Ethan!
关于家庭的故事
a story about family...
关于生存的故事
a story about survival.
《传世》前情提要
Previously on Extant:
很高兴你回来了  莫莉
It's a pleasure to have you back, Molly.
我们很想念你
You were missed.
她丈夫约翰今天向你的董事会做了报告
Her husband John gave a presentation to your board today,
但是被拒绝提供资金
but was denied funding.
你的善举能让我们更接近这一家人
A gesture from you could put us closer to the family.
他在我来之前去世了
He passed away before I came on board.
-你们很亲近吗  -是的
- Were you close? - Yeah.
-他是个好人  -我是戈登·科恩
- He was a good guy. - I'm Gord Kern.
新的副局长
The new deputy director.
我是想叫你给我一些时间
I'm asking for some time.
-就算为了朋友  -莫莉  报告是直接
- As my friend. - Molly, this goes
递交给斯帕克斯局长的  我不能撒谎啊
straight to Director Sparks-- I can't lie.
我们必须马上走
We have to go right now.
-不  -伊森
- No! - Ethan!
-他变了  -你也变了
- He's changed. - And so have you.
家人分别的久了就会产生这种结果
That's the consequence of our family being apart for so long.
-关系需要时间才能恢复  -我在努力了呀
- It takes time to reconnect. - Well, I'm trying.
我觉得你离我们越来越远了
It feels like you're pulling away from us.
救救我
灭绝
■
本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译
禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
翻译：爱卿遛小鸟 Reginamoon 王大可 DustD 暴龙蛋
翻译：滚成一个团子 Silence 小欠 木浅薰 迷失绽放
时间轴：贝贝 信徒 西西   校对：圈圈
后期：MythCreator   总监：米小勒  圈圈
一切都好吗
Everything all right?
都好  我只是
Yeah. Yeah. I'm, you know,
还有点晕
just... a little fuzzy, still.
给你  标准冲泡  准时到
Here. 140, on the dot.
好香啊
Oh, it smells good.
知道在太空中最艰苦的事是什么吗
You know the hardest thing about being in space?
咖啡太难喝了
The coffee's awful.
这是最艰苦的事
That's the hardest thing?
当然了
Absolutely.
好了  伊森在哪
Okay. Okay. Where's Ethan?
-还在睡  -好吧
- Uh, still in bed. - Okay, well,
我开始做早餐  你叫他起来穿衣服  好吗
I'm gonna start breakfast and you get him dressed, okay?
这就去
On it.
我知道你没时间为安德鲁的派对买东西
I knew you wouldn't have time to go shopping for Andrew's party.
伊森要给他什么
What's Ethan giving him?
一款电玩  《太空入侵》
A video game: Space Invasion.
不错  谢谢你了
Nice. Thanks for doing that.
没事  不管你干什么  别碰蛋糕
Sure. Hey, whatever you do, stay away from the cake.
我晚点带你去安德烈餐厅吃午餐
I'm taking you to a late lunch at Endre's.
都已经安排好了
Uh, already been arranged.
第一次约会的位子  就在露台上
First date table, right on the patio,
巧克力舒芙蕾
chocolate souffle.
为了什么
What's the occasion?
我们有很多事要庆祝
We have a lot to celebrate.
你的安全归来  我的新实验室
Your safe return, my new lab.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我觉得棒极了
I think that's great.
这个我也帮你搞定了
I took care of this for you, too.
十点博物馆的聚会
Party at the museum at 10:00,
你一点钟带伊森来找我
you bring Ethan to me by 1:00,
我带他去见安本
I take him to meet Yasumoto,
那时我俩绝对都需要喝上一杯了
by that point we'll definitely both need a drink.
然后就该去安德烈餐厅吃午饭了
And that's where lunch at Endre's comes in.
所有都在这里面的提醒事项上了
It's everything in here with the reminders.
我得走了
I better get going.
-等等  -怎么了
- Hey, hey. - Mm-hmm?
得注意点
Got to look sharp.
这样好多了
That's better...
"注意点"是什么意思
What does "Look sharp" mean?
就是这样
This is looking sharp.
拜拜
Bye.
要乖哦
Behave.
好吧...
Well...
就剩我们妇女儿童了
guess it's just us chickens.
山姆
Sam.
-艾伦  -早上好
- Alan. - Good morning.
-有什么事吗  -莫莉的结果
- What can I do for you? - Molly's results.
她的回归体检
Her reentry physical.
你知道实验室什么时候能出结果吗
Any idea when we're gonna hear from the lab?
今晚应该就能拿到了
Well, we should have them by tonight.
最迟明天
Tomorrow at the latest.
她肯定不会有问题的
I'm sure she'll be fine.
我一拿到结果就马上给你
You'll have them as soon as I have them.
谢谢
Thank you.
不客气
Sure.
-早上好  朱莉  -早上好
- Morning, Julie. - Good morning.
我帮你带了咖啡
I got you coffee.
莫莉在家呢  喝过了
Molly's home. Made a pot.
真好  欢迎来到我们的新家
Great. Welcome to our new home.
你感觉怎样
What do you think?
是吧
Right?
编程在这里
Programming is here,
已经开始运行并且开始写我们的新协议了
already up and writing our new protocols.
制造和组装终于能即时进入
Manufacture and Assembly finally have instant access
打印机和学习中心了
to the printers and the learning centers.
-你几点到这儿的  -早上五点
- What time did you get here? - 5:00.
分享传递关怀
Sharing is caring.
你好呀  牛人
Hey, Tops.
我们这组合又重聚了
Band's back together.
的确如此
Yes, it is.
我负责人体打印机
Hey, flesh printer goes by me.
我们的办公室在这边
Our station is here.
当头儿总得有些福利  不是吗
There have to be some perks to being in charge, right?
从你的车库到那神奇的仓库  到...
From your garage to that wonder of a warehouse to...
这里
this?
怎么了
What?
我只是好奇
I'm just wondering
你对安本说了什么让他改变了主意
what you said to Yasumoto to turn it around.
我本人也想知道这个
I'd like to know that myself.
多德女士
Ms. Dodd.
你什么时候玩这个玩得这么好了
When did you get so good at this?
你不在的时候我和爸爸还有朱莉经常玩
I played a lot with Dad and Julie while you were gone.
你想试试吗
Do you want to try?
好啊
Yeah.
当然
Sure.
好吧
Okay.
天啊  我都忘了这个有多难了
Oh, man, I forgot how hard this was.
对不起
I'm sorry.
爸爸说玩这个得耐心点
Dad says you have to be patient.
-是啊  -你想再试一次吗
- Yeah. - Do you want to try again?
我得去为安德鲁的派对做准备了
I have to go get ready for Andrew's party.
我喜欢去博物馆
I like the museum.
我也喜欢
Me, too.
我像你这么大的时候
When I was your age,
那里是我全世界最喜欢的地方
that was my favorite place in the whole world.
但现在太空是你最喜欢的地方了
But space is your favorite place now.
是吗
Right?
不
Nope.
是这里
It's right here.
跟你和爸爸在一起
With you and Dad.
发射倒计时
Countdown to liftoff.
三十分钟
T-minus 30.
一个人工生命在此诞生
A Humanich is born here.
他们在开始的几年以程序的形式存在
They live their first few years as a program,
成长学习  就像我们一样
growing and learning, much the same way we do.
就像你的女儿一样
The same way your daughter did.
我女儿三岁前不生活在一个盒子里
My daughter didn't spend her first three years in a box.
是的  但她的大脑却在用那段时间
No, but her brain spent that time
书写自己的程序
writing its own sort of program.
这也正是我们在这里做的事
And that's exactly what we're doing here.
我们让大脑书写自己的程序
We allow a brain to write its programming
就像人类一样
just like a human would.
当一切成熟时
And when it's developed enough,
我们就把他放进一个身体中
we put him in a physical body.
-也可能是她  -也可能是她
- Or her. - Or her, exactly.
我希望你能明白这并没有什么可怕的
I-I hope you can see there's really nothing to fear here.
机器的崛起
The rise of the machines.
救我  救我
Help me. Help me.
我不担心机器人会摧毁我们  伍兹博士
I'm not worried about the robots destroying us, Dr. Woods.
我觉得我们自己也有能力那样做
I think we're perfectly capable of doing that ourselves.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我问你一个问题
Let me ask you a question.
如果你的机器能够那么近似于人类
If your machines become so human
以至于我们与他们建立了真正的心灵交流
that we establish genuine connection with them,
那会对我们已有的关系造成什么影响呢
what does that do to the one we have with each other?
我没有把这种情况当做是一个问题来看
I don't know that that's a reasonable concern.
那你应该花点时间和我女儿相处一下
Well, then you should spend some time with my daughter.
她与家里智能系统的关系比与我更亲近
She's closer to our home Verdisign system than she is with me.
人工生命是不同的
Well, Humanichs are different.
他们依旧是机器
They're still machines.
-他们不懂回报  -那你应该和我儿子
- They can't give back. - Then you should spend some time
相处一下  我觉得他会让你改变想法
with my son-- I think he could convince you otherwise.
我不是来改变想法的  伍兹博士
I didn't come here to be convinced, Dr. Woods.
我来这里是因为  出于某些奇怪的原因
I came here because, for some inexplicable reason,
安本先生绕过董事会资助了你的项目
Mr. Yasumoto went around the board to fund your project.
我来是想当面告诉你
I came to tell you face-to-face,
我不打算就此认输
I don't intend to take that lying down.
你不用那样做  斗争已经结束了
You don't have to. The war's over.
我赢了
I won.
谢谢你带我参观
Thank you for the tour.
不用担心她
Don't worry about her.
我们有安本的支持
We've got Yasumoto.
不止那样
We've got much more than that.
我们还有伊森
We've got Ethan.
没事的
It's okay.
他的进程速度上升了
His process speeds are picking up.
他要和妈妈去自然历史博物馆
Uh, he's going to the Natural History Museum with his mom.
只是兴奋而已
Just excited.
可能要处理的信息太多了
Probably a lot to take in.
妈妈
Mom?
你没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah.
我没事
I'm okay.
传世  第一季第二集
去跟他们一起玩吧
Why don't you go join them.
去吧
Go on.
莫莉
Molly,
太感谢你了
thank you so much.
安德鲁真的很想让伊森来
Andrew really wanted Ethan to come.
看看你啊
Wow, look at you.
对了  你还不知道
Oh, right, you didn't know.
十三个月里能发生很多事
A lot can happen in 13 months.
我听说伊森马上就要去学校了
I heard that Ethan's going to school soon.
他明天要去报到
He's got orientation tomorrow.
他可兴奋了
He's so excited.
让他进去是不是很难
Was it hard to get him in?
你知道的  约翰一直在和学校合作
Uh, well, you know, John's been working with the school.
-他们要去马里亚纳海沟  -我能也去吗
- They're going to the Mariana Trench. - Can I go, too?
我来带他们
I'll take them.
好啊
Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
谢谢你过来
Thanks for coming.
挺麻烦的
It wasn't easy.
斯帕克斯一直管我要你的检测结果
Sparks is breathing down my neck about your results.
到底是怎么回事
So what happened?
我不知道  我晕倒了  好吗
I don't know. I passed out, okay?
我的头震震欲裂
I had this pounding in my head,
然后肚子一阵痛  然后我就
and then I had this pain in my stomach and then I...
我不知道  我有了一种幻觉
I don't know, I had some kind of vision...
莫莉  我们得告诉斯帕克斯
Molly, we have to tell Sparks.
-不行  还不行  -我不明白
- No, not yet. - I don't understand.
我不知道能不能相信他
I don't know if I can trust him.
为什么
Why not?
哈蒙还活着
Harmon is alive.
-你在说什么  -他没有自杀
- What are you talking about? - He didn't kill himself.
我昨晚看到他了  当时我正在倒垃圾
I saw him last night. I was taking out the trash
然后他出现了  他告诉我
and there he was-- he told me
不要相信国际安全设备协会或任何人
not to trust the ISEA or anybody.
国际安全设备协会
The ISEA?
但他们是一家人啊  这是为什么
But they're family. Why?
我不知道  但是他很怕他们
I don't know. But he's so scared of 'em
甚至伪造了自己的死亡
he actually faked his own death.
他到底是怎么回事
What the hell is wrong with the guy?
他的脑扫描显示有异常
There were abnormalities in his brain scans,
像是某种神经病毒
some sort of neuro virus.
他从哪里感染的
That he got from where?
塞拉芬吗
The Seraphim?
我不知道
I don't know.
好吧
Okay.
那你知道什么
Well, what do you know?
我把你的脑扫描和他的做了对比
I compared your brain scans to his.
你的里边也出现了同样的异常
And you have the same abnormalities.
莫莉  发生在哈蒙·克雷格身上的情况
Molly, whatever happened to Harmon Kryger
正发生在你身上  这让我十分害怕
is happening to you, too, and that scares me.
有没有可能是我血液里的反应
Could a hysterical pregnancy actually show up
引起的癔病性怀孕
as a positive in my blood?
我是说有没有可能是我脑部的异常情况
I mean, could the abnormalities in my brain
导致的这一切
actually cause that?
跟你的脑部无关
This is not in your head.
你怀孕了
You are pregnant.
我尝试了十年
I tried for ten years.
都没怀上
I don't get pregnant.
但你现在确实怀孕了
But you are.
好吧
Okay.
我需要照超声波
I need an ultrasound.
我得确定
I need to know for sure.
好的
Okay.
但我不能把你的信息输入系统
I just cannot put you in the system.
我得找个其他...
I-I have to find a place where...
不会留下记录的地方
I can do this off the books.
-好的  -莫莉
- Okay. - Molly,
伊森不见了
we can't find Ethan.
我才一转身  他就没人影了
I turned around and he was gone.
-他之前在哪  -海洋生物大厅
- Where was he? - Marine Bio Hall.
快去吧
Go. Go.
请退后
Please step back.
进化链展示物不是互动展品
The Chain of Evolution is not an interactive display.
我知道你对尼安德特人很有兴趣
I see you are interested in the Neanderthal.
如果你愿意  我可以告诉你更多信息
I can tell you more about him, if you like.
好的
Okay.
尼安德特人在三万年前已经灭绝
Neanderthal Man went extinct about 30,000 years ago.
-什么意思  -灭绝就是不复存在
-"Extinct"? - "Extinct" Is to no longer exist.
他们为什么灭绝了
Why did they go extinct?
灭绝的原因有很多
Extinction happens for many reasons.
几乎在所有情况下  只有强者才能生存
In almost all cases, strong species survive
弱者自然就会被淘汰
and the weak ones die.
这叫适者生存
It's called survival of the fittest.
尼安德特人怎么了
What happened to the Neanderthal?
智人来到了尼安德特人生活的亚欧大陆上
Homo sapiens came to Eurasia, where the Neanderthals lived,
因为他们更强壮  头脑也更发达
and they were better able to survive
所以他们生存了下来
because they were stronger and smarter.
智人是什么
What's a Homo sapien?
智人是一个种群的名字
Homo sapien is the name of the species
现代人也属于它的一部分
that modern man is a part of.
比如  你就是智人
You, for example, are a Homo sapien.
不  我不是
No. I'm not.
不好意思
I apologize for my mistake.
那你是什么物种
What species are you?
伊森
Ethan!
终于找到你了
There you are.
这是我妈妈
This is my mom.
我知道你对尼安德特人很有兴趣
I see you are interested in the Neanderthal.
如果你愿意  我可以告诉你更多信息
I can tell you more about him, if you like.
不用了  谢谢  我们走
No, thank you. Come on. Let's go.
-再见  -祝你有个愉快的下午
- Bye. - Have a pleasant afternoon.
伊森  你不应该那样跑开的
Ethan, you know you shouldn't run off like that.
-我很担心你  -我知道
- I was worried. - I know.
我不小心走散的时候  爸爸也是这么说的
Dad said the same thing, that I'm not supposed to wander off.
我们要告诉他吗
Do we have to tell him?
不
No.
不用告诉他
We don't have to tell him.
就像个秘密样吗
Like a secret?
算是吧
Sort of.
爸爸说秘密不好
Dad says secrets are mean.
可能会是那样
Well, they can be.
但是有时人们保守秘密
But sometimes people keep secrets
是不想让别人担心
so that other people don't worry about things
他们无需担心的事
that they don't need to worry about.
像是爸爸如果知道你乱跑就会非常担心
Like Dad would be really worried if he knew you ran off.
如果他知道我昏倒了
And he'd be really worried
他也会很担心的
if he knew I fell down.
他为什么会担心呢
Why would that worry him?
这个嘛
Well...
他可能会觉得我生病了
he might think I'm sick.
那你生病了吗
Are you sick?
没有
No.
我只是因为刚回到地球而已
I'm just getting back to Earth, that's all.
那你感觉虚弱吗
Are you weak?
不是
No.
如果你替我保密我就也替你保密
So I'll keep your secret if you keep mine.
好的
Okay.
就这么说定了
Good deal.
我们走吧
Let's go.
怎么回事  本
What's going on, Ben?
我正在探测来自耀班的干扰
I'm detecting interference from the solar flare.
我要失去有你陪伴的愉快时光了吗
Am I gonna be losing the pleasure of your company?
哈蒙  在第三区有能量激增反应
Harmon, there's an energy surge in Sector Three.
与耀斑有关吗
Flare-related?
怎么回事  本
What's going on, Ben?
本
Ben?
妈妈
Mother?
你觉得怎样
What do you think?
这真是太令人难以置信了
Wow. I mean, this is unbelievable.
砸了几十亿买的东西还是很棒的
Amazing what a couple of billion buys.
亲爱的  你好啊
Hey, Rabbit.
你好  莫莉
Hey, Molly.
你好  朱莉
Hi, Julie.
派对怎么样
How was the party?
好极了
Great.
小伙子
Hey, bud.
你想看看你的新胳膊吗
Want to see your new arm?
我会变得很高大的
I'm gonna be big.
我会把它装上去
I'll hook it up,
让你能抠到自己的鼻子的
let you pick your own nose.
约翰  抱歉打扰
John, sorry to interrupt.
现在是您和安本先生的会面时间
It's time for your meeting with Mr. Yasumoto.
我们走吧  小家伙
Let's go, buddy.
伊森
Ethan.
你会很棒的
You're gonna be great.
祝我们好运
Wish us luck.
-祝你们好运  -好运
- Good luck. - Good luck.
-午饭时见  -好的
- See you at lunch. - Okay.
那么  祝贺你  因为
Well, you know what, congratulations because...
我知道  这  这是不是很疯狂
I know. It's-it's so crazy, right?
对伊森来说你回来真是太好了
It's so great for Ethan to have you back.
整整13个月
God, 13 months.
真是太久了
That's such a long time.
对啊
Yeah.
我很高兴回来
But, you know what, I'm glad to be back.
我可以带你周围看看
Well, I could show you around...
其实我真的有事要做
Actually, I have something that I really have to do, so, um...
-改天吧  -当然
- Rain check? - Sure.
伊森告诉我
Uh, Ethan told me
我不在的时候  他和你玩得很开心
he had so much fun with you while I was gone, and...
谢谢你
Well, thank you.
客气了
It's no problem.
回头见
See you.
拜
Bye.
喜欢恐龙吗
Do you like dinosaurs?
喜欢  先生
Yes, sir.
他一早上都待在自然历史博物馆
He spent the morning at the Natural History Museum.
你对科学有兴趣吗
Are you interested in science?
我爸妈都是科学家
My mom and dad are both scientists.
我知道  还是很棒的科学家
Yes, I know. Very good ones.
喜欢你的新设备吗
How do you like your new facilities?
那些设备在每个方面都非常出色
They're perfect. In every way.
-太好了  -再次感谢你
- I'm glad. - Thank you again.
我觉得我该告诉你  今天
I feel like I should mention I had a visit
你们董事会有位成员来找我了
from one of your board members today.
费米  费米·多德女士
Ms.... Ms. Femi Dodd.
她好像很困扰
She seemed troubled.
多德女士不像我对未来抱有如此乐观的态度
Ms. Dodd doesn't share my optimistic view of the future.
伍兹博士  我先问你个问题
Let me ask you, Dr. Woods:
十年后
ten years from now,
或二十年后  你认为人工生命会怎么样
or 20, what do you see happening with Humanichs?
我觉得它们会和人类肩并肩地生活工作
I see them living and working side by side with humans.
跟我们毫无区别
No different from us.
他真的很惊人
He really is astonishing.
你妻子回来后怎么样了
How is your wife since her return?
莫莉  她  她很好
Molly? She's, uh... she's good.
还在恢复状态中  那趟任务去得比较久
Still recovering. It was a long mission.
我想见见她
I'd love to meet her.
我们一起吃顿饭吧
We'll have to arrange a dinner.
当然  也带上伊森
And, of course, you'll bring Ethan.
那就太好了
That would be great.
伍兹博士
Dr. Woods.
本  我需要访问塞拉芬的
Hey, Ben, I need access to security footage
安全监控录像
from the Seraphim, please.
当然  莫莉  你想看你任务中的哪一部分
Sure, Molly. What part of your mission would you like to view?
不是我的  是哈蒙·克雷格的
Uh, not mine. Harmon Kryger's.
有什么具体要求吗
What is your specific request?
他的任务中出现过一次太阳耀斑
There was a solar flare on his mission.
从耀斑撞击之前开始
Take me to the time right before the flare hit
播放一次给我看
and run it through, please.
请稍等
Just a moment.
抱歉  你没有访问监控录像的权限
I'm sorry. Access to that footage is above your clearance.
拒绝访问
那实验录像呢  我有权限访问吗
What about the experiment cams? Do I have access to those?
-有  -好  给我播放实验室B摄像头的录像
- Yes. - Okay. Take me to Lab Cam B.
同一个时间段
Same time frame, please.
正在载入录像
Loading footage.
快进
Fast-forward.
播放
Play.
给我播放同一时间段实验室A摄像头录像
Take me to Lab Cam A. Same time frame.
正在载入
Loading.
他在那挡住什么东西
What is he barricading there?
我不确定
I'm not sure.
那扇门后有什么
What's behind that door?
抱歉  莫莉
I'm sorry, Molly.
我接收到指令  终止这次会话
I've been directed to terminate this session.
注意  您的芯片已被移出
Attention. Your tether has become dislodged.
无法监测您的医疗信息
Your medical information can no longer be monitored.
莫莉
Molly!
上车
Get in!
快  上车  上车
Come on. Get in. Get in the car.
上车
Get in the car.
我们追踪了她的监控芯片信号
We followed the signal of her monitoring tether.
她把芯片留在洗手间了
She left it in the bathroom.
她不见了吗
She's gone?
而且离开之前
And before she left,
她用我们的系统查看了
she used our system to access
克雷格的任务录像
footage from Kryger's mission.
需要我把她带回来吗
Do you want me to bring her back in?
我们就扩大一点她的活动范围吧
Let's give her a little more rope.
我得打电话给我丈夫  他一直在等我
I gotta call my husband. He's been waiting.
这里没有信号  所以我才选这里
Phones don't work out here. It's part of the appeal.
好吧
Okay.
这是怎么回事
What is going on?
我想告诉他们我所看到的东西
I tried to tell them what I saw.
刚开始我以为
At first I thought, well,
他们就是  就是不相信我
that they just... they just don't believe me.
但没那么简单
But it's more than that.
他们说我精神分裂  疯了
They said I was schizophrenic. Crazy.
我就开始以为也许真的是我疯了
I started to think maybe I was crazy.
我试过查看你的任务录像
I tried to access footage from your mission.
但本不允许
Ben locked me out.
他们不想让我看到的是什么
So what is it they don't want me to see?
我看到了某个人
I saw someone.
妈妈
Mother?
不...  不要
N-No... No.
妈妈
Mother.
不
No.
气闸排除已启动
Airlock evacuation initiated.
不
No.
舱门已封闭
Door armed.
他们让我再次看到她
They made me see her again,
就是她临死前的样子
just like she was before she died.
我知道那是真的
I know it was real.
我知道我看到了什么  也知道我做了什么
I know what I saw, and I know what I did.
哈蒙  山姆对比了我们的脑部扫描
Harmon... Sam compared our brain scans.
它们都显示了同一种异常情况
They're both showing the same abnormalities.
那可能是导致我们有幻象的原因
That could be the reason for our visions.
异常是什么引起的
What caused the abnormalities?
他们把我们暴露到辐射下面了吗
Did-did they expose us to radiation?
他们  他们对我们注射东西了吗  是什么
Did they... did they dose us with something? What?
我不知道他们为什么要这么做
I don't know why they would do something like that.
为了测试外太空对人体的影响
To test the effects of deep space on the body.
为了看看我们在强压之下的表现
To see how we perform under stress.
我们以为我们在做实验
We thought we were doing experiments?
其实我们是实验对象
We were the experiments.
我们需要证据
Well, we need proof.
因为现在  我们手上只有我们的故事
Okay? Because right now, all we have is our stories.
看看我的故事给我带来了什么
Look what my story got me.
他们会监听你的电话
They'll bug your phone,
他们会跟踪你
they'll follow you,
强制隔离你
they'll force you into quarantine,
就算你告诉别人  也没人会相信你
and if you tell anybody, nobody will believe you,
甚至是你最爱的那些人
not even the people you love.
克雷格见到了他母亲
Kryger saw his mother?
没错  她都去世将近30年了
Yup. She's been dead for almost 30 years.
你看到的是谁
Who did you see?
马库斯
Marcus.
莫莉  很遗憾
Molly. I'm so sorry.
他们到底在做什么样的实验
You know, what kind of experiment could they be doing
会让我们见到自己爱过而且失去了的人
where we both would see people that we loved and lost?
我不知道  真的不知道
I don't know. I really don't know.
他完全就是他死去那天的模样
He looked exactly as he did the morning he died,
在他离开家之前
before he left the house.
那感觉太真实
It was real.
所以你才一直不告诉约翰吗
Is that why you haven't told John?
我该告诉约翰什么
I tell John what, exactly?
我在太空昏迷了一段时间
That, uh... I had a psychotic episode in space,
或者我出现幻觉见到了我死去的男友
or that I had a vision of my dead boyfriend and now
结果现在还怀着我都不知道是什么的东西
I'm pregnant with something I can't explain?
真的假的啊
I mean, really?
山姆  我很害怕
Sam, I'm scared.
一旦我告诉他  一切都会改变
That the minute I tell him, everything's gonna be different.
莫莉  他很爱你  真的爱你
Molly... he loves you. So much.
我知道
Yeah, but...
但我得了解的深入些再说
I need to know more.
设备很老旧了  不过能用
The equipment's old, but it works.
坐上来
Hop up here.
我会尽量让你舒服些的
I'm gonna try to make you as comfortable as possible.
准备好了吗
You good?
好了
Yeah. All right.
开始吧
Here we go.
-把衣服撩起来好吗  -好的
- Um, can you lift up your shirt? - Yeah.
好的  放松  这会有点凉
All right, just relax. This is gonna be cold.
-而且会稍稍有点压迫感  -好的
- And you are gonna feel some pressure. - Okay.
在哪呢
Where are you?
找到了
Here.
什么
What?
你自己看吧
See for yourself.
一切正常
Completely normal.
14周大的人类胎儿
14-week-old human fetus.
心跳也正常
With a baby's heartbeat.
莫莉
Molly.
你对我做了什么
What did you do to me?
我不明白你的意思
I don't know what you mean.
是吗
Really?
我怀孕14周了
Well, I'm 14 weeks pregnant.
而14周之前  我还一个人在太空
And 14 weeks ago, I was in space. Alone.
-你确定吗  -百分之百确定
- Are you sure? - 100%.
我们是好朋友  对吗
We're really good friends, right?
-是啊  -那么请你
- Yeah. - Then, just, please...
告诉我你对我做了什么
tell me what you did to me.
莫莉
Molly...
我什么也没干
I didn't do anything.
我不会骗你的
I wouldn't lie to you.
国际安全设备协会绝不会干这种事的
The ISEA would never do something like that.
作为朋友我更不会这样对你
I wouldn't do it to you, as a friend.
何况本来就是我让你参加这个计划的
Hell, I brought you into this program.
你是我的家人
You're family.
如果不是你做的  那是谁做的
Well, if you didn't do it, then who did it?
如果有人对你这么做
If it was someone here,
我会找出是谁  我向你保证
I'll find out. I promise you.
你本该保护我们的
You were supposed to protect us.
莫莉怀孕改变了一切
Molly's pregnancy changes everything.
我不确定克雷格什么时候回来的
I wasn't sure when Kryger came back.
他的行为太古怪了
His behavior was too erratic.
但无疑他那时他跟莫莉在一起
But with Molly there can be no doubt.
你认为我们找到他们了
You think we found them?
我认为他们已经来了
I think they're already here.
如果这是真的
If that's true...
如果他们来了
if they're here...
我们会力所不及
we're way out of our depth.
我们没有应对计划
We have no plan for this.
一步步来
One step at a time.
我们做了什么
What have we done?
我会告诉你我们做了什么
I'll tell you what we've done.
我们向凯蒂的牺牲致敬
We've honored Katie's sacrifice.
这一切皆由你女儿开始  艾伦
This all started with your daughter, Alan.
你该感到自豪
You should be proud.
你的预期寿命是一百年零两天
你马上到楼下来吗
Are you coming downstairs soon?
看我们做了什么
Look what we did.
给你留了剩菜
I've got leftovers.
不知道蛋奶酥可不可以再加热
I'm not sure the souffle can reheat.
约翰  对不起
John... I'm sorry.
我跟丹尼在实验室
Y... I was at the lab with Danny
然后山姆来了
and then, uh, Sam came by...
你为什么不给我打电话  我很担心你
Why didn't you call me? I was worried.
因为我不能  知道吗
Because I couldn't, okay?
就这样吗
That's it?
我就是不能  对不起
I just couldn't. I'm sorry.
如果你还没准备好
If you're not ready to talk about
说你的经历  没事
what's going on with you, that's fine.
如果你需要时间  我可以等
If you need time, take it.
你不需要自己一个人扛着
You don't have to do this by yourself.
你回来了  有我们在身边
You're here now. With us.
我知道
I know.
我给你加热一盘
I'll heat you up a plate.
他需要知道你没事
He-he needs to know you're all right.
好
Okay.
我给你画了张画
I drew you a picture.
是吗  可以给我看看吗
You did? Can I see?
我把一家人放在飞船里  那样他们会安全
I put the family in the spaceship, so that they'd be safe.
为什么不安全
Safe from what?
灭绝
Extinction.
Extinction?
你哪里学到的这个词
Where'd you learn about that?
今天去博物馆的时候
At the museum today.
是更强  更聪明的物种生存的地方
It's where the stronger, smarter species survive.
没事的  我替你保守秘密了
It's okay... I kept your secret.
来看看...你还画了什么
Let's see... what else did you draw here?